Skylar Harwell

Accomplishments

As a Team Lead, I lead the TSO-FORMS team of 24 associates in day-to-day operations & training. I am responsible for implementing multiple process improvements to streamline work & increase efficiencies by updating & creating various SOPs, Process Maps, & Automated processes. I assist in agile team sprints to identify Future State processes & improvements by researching & reviewing process & procedures to ensure production efficiencies are gained.

Technical Skills & Abilities

- Word, Excel, Outlook, OneNote, SharePoint, Visio
- HTML, JavaScript,
- Understanding of Agile Methodology
- Knowledgeable in identifying & creating SOP updates.
- Adept in the initial creation of SOPs & Process Maps.
- Proficient in cross-communication between departments & leading Enterprise initiatives virtually.

Professional Experience

Services Coordinator – Administrative Services – Technical Services

08/24/2019 - Present

- Responsible for multiple Process Updates to maximize efficiency allowing team to not fill open positions & reduce staff from over 40 associates to the current 24 with no loss in production
- Tasked with creating Quality Assurance Review process to quantify individual's accuracy in production by creating metrics & Quality documents
- Worked with multiple Agile teams to research current & future state processes to analyze & implement improvements & provide recommendations to updates

Technician – Administrative Services – Technical Services

11/17/2018 - 08/23/2019

- Maintained production at a high level processing & approving multiple forms from Enterprise associates
- Multiple times was the top producer on the team often exceeding the average by double the next Technician

PIM Technician - Administrative Services - Document Services

09/26/2015 - 11/16/2018

- Executed a reorganization effort in Printing, Inserting, & Mailing (PIM) stock department to reallocate space & ensure organization of over 300 inserts & policy documents & removing over 150 unused items to maintain quality control & inventory
- Tasked with On-Boarding multiple technicians into the Cancellation process in PIM to reduce Overtime hours & increase quality handling of highly sensitive mail
- Responsible for analyzing & creating a notification process to phase out of a line of business that was expected to take over a week & was completed in less than a business day

Claim Associate-Express - Property Claims

12/09/2013 - 09/25/2018

Associate of Arts

- Responsible for contacting & servicing claims under the Green demand pool
- Maintained productivity & consistently exceeded production & quality goals

Education

CPCU Designation (In Progress)
Expected completion 2023
Valdosta State University December 2007
Bachelor of Arts
Abraham Baldwin Agricultural College June 2004

Skylar Harwell

Completed Projects

Movie Information app "GeorgiaScreen"

- A movie search app that takes the input of a movie title and provides info including Plot Summary, Actors, Directors, etc. and provides additional info about the actors with links to see where to stream these movies.
 - o HTML & JavaScript
 - o **GeorgiaScreen**

Weather Generator App

- App that takes the name of a city and provides weather information for current and the next 5 days. App also saves your searches for quick reference.
 - o HTML & JavaScript
 - o Weather Generator

JavaScript Timed Quiz

- Fun little quiz about JavaScript that allows you to track a high score and compete with friends!
 - o HTML & JavaScript
 - o Timed Quiz

Outside of Work

While not working I am an avid baker of all things from cookies, cakes & pies, to breads & pastries. I also spend my time working on sculpting & casting items & figures in resin & helping my wife with her art endeavors.